CARVED : THE SLIT-MOUTHED WOMAN
A boy in our neighboring school saw the slit-mouthed woman .
No kidding I
Where ?
He was playing alone in a park near his school , when he saw ...
a strange woman standing in front of him .
Was she tall with long hair ?
Yes , and her mouth was covered with ...
a white mask and she wore a long coat .
And then what ?
But as the boy was about to run away ...
DATA BOOK : THE SLIT-MOUTHED WOMAN
the woman suddenly asked him in a strange voice , " Am I pretty ? "
Then she took off the white mask and ...
revealed her mouth that was slit up to her ears !
When you 're caught , she takes you to her hideout ...
and cuts your mouth with scissors .
The slit-mouthed woman has become merciless these days .
Stop talking about such things .
Does it remind you of the old days ?
When I was in high school ...
the same rumor spread all over Japan .
Did you know ?
The rumor first started right here in this town .
- Really ? - Yeah , really .
And now the slit-mouthed woman is back in town .
Yuki , will you do some shopping for me ?
I don 't want to .
They say the slit-mouthed woman appears in the park at five .
Come on ...
- I 'll go then . - Bye .
It 's true .
Hey .
What do we do she really appears ?
We should run , I guess .
But you 're slow . She 'll get you .
I wish the slit-mouthed woman would take you away from me !
Why don 't you say something ? Cat got your tongue ?
Don 't just stand there .
Say something .
Why are you so quiet ?
Open your lips .
Do you want me to slit your mouth ?
- Do you think it 'll hurt ? - It sure will .
Of course .
Come on kids , you 'd better get back home .
Yes , Ms. Yamashita .
- Good bye . - Bye .
No gossiping about the slit-mouthed woman .
- Mr. Matsuzaki . - Hello .
- How are you getting along ? - Okay .
- It 's tough starting in a new school . - I guess .
I 'll go check the roof .
AM I PRETTY ?
What is it ?
Stay calm !
Am I ...
pretty ?
- Is it over ? - I think so .
That was a big one .
What time is it ?
It 's already past five .
I see no slit-mouthed woman .
Good morning .
Have you heard ?
The slit-mouthed woman disappeared with a boy yesterday .
- Really ? - Yep .
But on TV , they said it 's someone dressed like the slit-mouthed woman .
- Don 't believe what they say . - He 's right .
But that 's what they said .
Masatoshi .
Have you gathered information on the slit-mouthed woman ?
No , I haven 't .
Look at her .
The slit-mouthed woman !
They say her next victim is someone from school .
Then I must be the one .
Mika , don 't say such a thing .
But that would make someone happy .
Line up , the assembly is about to begin .
You 're at the front .
Today , classes will end at noon and you will go home in groups .
About the incident that occurred at our neighboring school ...
it 's only natural that you should be afraid .
However , we must keep calm .
And remember to follow the rules .
Never gossip about the slit-mouthed woman .
Never talk to people you don 't know .
Listen carefully to your parents at home .
And never go out without permission .
You look exactly like her .
You kidnapped that boy .
Can 't talk with your mouth slit ?
Where are you hiding him ?
You did it , right ?
Cut it out !
It 's none of your business .
Mika , let 's see your mouth . You wouldn 't mind , would you ?
Don 't !
Good morning .
What 's going on ?
Hello .
Hi , kids .
Thank you very much .
It 's no trouble .
Good bye .
Bye , Natsuki .
Bye-bye .
- Here you are . - You 're back .
We 'll break up from here .
Remember to be careful . Good bye .
- Bye . - Thank you .
You 're welcome . Bye .
- Bye . - Good bye .
- Thank you . - You 're welcome .
Thank you .
Good bye .
Let 's go .
What is it ?
Something wrong ?
Isn 't that your mother ?
Ms. Yamashita .
I was meaning to go , but I got caught up at work .
It 's okay . We 've just arrived .
Say good bye to your teacher .
Go on .
What 's the matter ?
I 'll come home later .
You can 't stay out alone .
I 'll be with her a little longer and make sure she gets home .
But ...
No trouble at all . We won 't be long .
Right , Mika ?
That 's all for today . Thank you for your cooperation .
- Thank you . - Thank you .
Thank you .
- Bye . - Good bye .
Be careful .
Bye .
- Thanks . - Thank you .
Am I ...
pretty ?
Did you quarrel with your mother , Mika ?
If so , I could help you make up with her .
- Ms. Yamashita . - Yes ?
Do mothers dislike their children ?
Some mothers might .
But I 'm sure that 's not the case with your mother .
Why ?
Just now , when you didn 't look at her she seemed truly sad .
That 's because she loves you .
Did she do that ?
I won 't let that happen to you , never again .
Mother does hate me .
No , she doesn 't . I know it .
She loves you , Mika .
Sometimes love can be so strong that people get carried away and ...
I hate my mother .
Don 't say such a thing !
Mika !
Don 't go .
Please !
So , she was wearing a mask like that , right ?
But her mouth ...
Would you come to the police station with us ?
- Let go of me ! - Mrs. Sasaki !
Pull yourself together .
Calm down .
We should stay at home . The kidnapper might call you .
Where is Mika ? Is she safe ?
My Mika .
Mika ...
- Mrs. Sasaki ! - Mrs. Sasaki !
Mrs. Sasaki .
Are you alright ?
An elephant .
A panda .
This is Ono .
It 's me . I know it 's late .
It 's you . Something the matter ?
No , not really .
I just wanted to talk to Ai . Is she already asleep ?
Yeah , she is .
I see .
Do you think she 's still reluctant to see me ?
She says she doesn 't want to see you .
I understand . Sorry .
Bye .
Is that so ?
You like Daddy more than Mommy , don 't you , Ai ?
Tell me the truth .
I like Daddy . I hate Mommy because you hit me .
I 'm sorry !
I didn 't mean to . Come here .
Go talk to her .
I will .
Mrs. Sasaki .
You 'd better rest . We 'll wake you if there 's news .
But I can 't sleep .
My heart keeps pounding .
HELP US FIND MIKA !
Ever since I lost my husband in an accident ...
things changed between Mika and me .
If I had been good to her ...
Mika would have come straight home .
I n Kanagawa , Midoriyama City ...
a series of kidnapping has occurred .
A search is underway for the two missing children .
The Kanagawa Police ...
are putting more people on the team hoping for a quick recovery .
THE SUSPECT 'S PROFILE
This is Shizukawa East Park where Fumiaki Ogawa was kidnapped .
He was abducted by someone disguised as the slit-mouthed woman .
Yesterday , a woman who looked like her ...
was seen kidnapping Mika Sasaki .
What could be the reason for kidnapping children in a disguise ?
What 's the matter ?
Did Mommy do it ?
I 've caught a cold .
Are you okay ?
- I 'll go buy some medicine . - Alright .
- Bye . - Bye .
The park where Fumiaki was kidnapped was seldom used ...
and there were only two of his friends at the time .
The next day , Mika Sasaki was kidnapped .
She was abducted before the eyes of her teacher ...
who had ...
I have some fliers of Mika .
And ... What 's up ... ?
Come on in .
They want to pass them out , too .
We 'd like to help .
SCHOOL CLOSED FOR THE DAY
I 'm terribly sorry .
It 's only a temporary suspension .
Please try and stay quiet during this period .
I will . Excuse me .
Ms. Yamashita .
Mr. Matsuzaki .
Could I ... talk to you privately ?
Then , you 've seen the woman 's face ?
That 's right .
But what 's that got to do with you ?
Please ...
Take a look at this picture .
She looks like her .
I thought so .
Who is she ?
What is this all about ?
Tell me if you know something . I want to help Mika .
Am I ...
pretty ?
What 's the matter ?
Excuse me .
Mr. Matsuzaki !
What are you doing ?
Who was that woman ?
Please get off .
I won 't . Not unless you tell me .
She is the kidnapper . We should notify the police .
That picture 's 30 years old .
Whenever a child is kidnapped ...
I hear a woman 's strange voice inside my head .
Can you believe that ?
I don 't know what 's going on .
But I 've just heard it again .
I 'm heading towards it .
This is Tsugawa Town , an hour 's drive from Shizukawa Town .
The children here are terrorized by the rumor of the slit-mouthed woman .
A friend told me that she 's immortal , that she can 't be killed .
My friend said that ...
she saw the split-mouthed woman in a nearby park .
There 's a house with a red roof somewhere . That 's her hideout .
There are rumors going around about her hideout .
Who is it ?
Masatoshil It 's Matsuzaki .
What is it , Mr. Matsuzaki ?
Open the door !
Don 't !
Am I ...
pretty ?
Masatoshi .
Are you alright ?
I 'm okay .
Thank God .
What 's wrong ?
Who is she ?
KAZUKO YOSHIDA
Mommy 's late .
I wonder what she 's doing .
I wonder what .
You 'll find the police station around the corner .
Okay .
Ms. Yamashita .
I 'm going to the dead lady 's house to look for Mika .
Will you come ?
Mr. Matsuzaki .
Is the slit-mouthed woman gone for good ?
I don 't know .
Ms. Yamashita , this may come in handy .
Thanks .
Where could she be ?
Are you Mrs. Yoshida 's ... ?
Mommy 's not home .
She 'll be home soon . Please come back later .
They say their father will be back by evening .
I 've killed their mother .
The younger girl was about the same age as my daughter .
My daughter 's with my ex-husband . I got divorced last year .
She likes him more , so ...
I 've never told anyone about this , but I want you to know .
I just saw her with my own eyes and I know for sure .
Her name is Taeko Matsuzaki .
She 's ...
my mother .
When my brothers and I were small ...
we used to be severely beaten by our mother .
Everyday was a nightmare .
Before long , my brother and sister were gone .
So was my mother .
They all disappeared .
Soon after that , the slit-mouthed woman 's rumor started .
A tall woman with long hair , wearing a mask .
When I first heard this , I immediately thought of my mother .
By that time , I 'd been sent to a foster home ...
but I was always afraid to go outside .
And after all these years , she 's come back again .
The woman I saw just now was definitely ...
my mother .
That lady must 've been possessed by her .
So there may be more victims ?
Am I ...
pretty ?
I have to go .
Take me with you .
People are afraid to play in the park . Let 's go find a crowd .
Okay .
Let 's hurry .
Right .
Are you alright ?
It 'll pass .
Are you sure the voice came from here ?
I thought so but ...
I can 't hear it anymore .
Wait , I hear it distantly .
From where ?
I can 't figure out which direction .
Let 's see if we can find the place as we drive along .
Right .
Mika ?
Please , don 't hurt me !
You 're Mom , aren 't you ?
Stop .
U ntie me !
Off we go .
- Did you enjoy playing with Grandpa ? - Yep .
I 'm glad you did .
- A little tired , huh ? - Yep .
Grandpa , what 's that ?
Don 't look !
The body found was that of a boy , right ?
Mika is safe , isn 't she ?
So far .
We 're searching the area thoroughly .
I see .
Can I go outside to breath fresh air ?
Yes . But don 't go too far .
I won 't .
Don 't worry . I 'm sure Mika will come back .
But the boy died .
Don 't say that .
Mika .
Where are you ?
Mika ?
Mika , come out .
- Mika ? - Mika .
- Mika ? Where are you ? - Mika ?
No ...
This can 't be ... !
Natsuki ! Natsuki !
Why won 't you talk ?
You know this is very important , don 't you ?
Mika 's life is in danger .
What did you see ?
Masatoshi , speak .
Alright . I 'll tell you everything I know .
Searching the body of the missing boy , Fumiaki Ogawa ...
a 10-year-old girl , Natsuki Tamura was found in the same town ...
sitting in a park with a severe cut on her face .
She 's in critical condition .
Isn 't Natsuki a girl from your class ?
Police are looking for a connection between this incident ...
and the murder of the housewife ...
This is bad .
I N S P E C T I O N
Stay cool .
- Good evening . - Hello .
Your driver 's license , please .
- Thank you . - No problem .
- Excuse me . - Yes ?
We teach at Shizukawa Elementary .
How 's the girl found in the park ?
Her condition is now stable .
Good .
Any new information on Mika Sasaki ?
There 's nothing to tell at the moment .
It is gossipy and unreliable .
DATA BOOK : THE SLIT-MOUTHED WOMAN
" She appears in the park near Higashi Elementary .
" The next victim is a girl from Shizukawa .
It 's impossible to kill the slit-mouthed woman . "
This is all true .
I know .
Is there anything that would lead us to Mika ?
How 's this ?
" The slit-mouthed woman hides children in a house with a red roof . "
A red roof ...
That 's hard to narrow down .
It could be ...
The house I used to live in when I was a child .
Did it have a red roof ?
Mika is probably in the slit-mouthed woman 's hideout .
You should listen to the rumors .
If we do this carefully , we might get more information on her whereabouts .
But there are thousands of houses with red roofs .
Is anybody home ?
Hello ?
May I speak with you ?
Please .
What do you want ?
Could I have a word with you ?
I 'm the mother of this missing child .
I was wondering if you knew something .
Yes .
Would you please tell me anything you know ?
Any rumor of the slit-mouthed woman ?
I know ! I 've heard about her hideout .
- Hey ! - It 's okay .
The slit-mouthed woman 's hideout , right ?
Yes , a deserted house with a red roof .
HIDEOUT , RED ROOF , DESERTED HOUSE
Do you know where it is ?
On top of Childbeck Hill .
- Childbeck Hill ? - Yep .
We go up from here ?
CHILD BECK HILL
Mika .
Where are you ?
Are you in here ?
Mika .
Mika ?
What 's wrong ?
I remember now .
How my mother became ...
the slit-mouthed woman .
Noboru ...
I 've done it again .
Noboru .
I didn 't mean to .
Did it hurt ?
Forgive me .
Please , Noboru .
It hurt , didn 't it ?
I 'm so sorry .
No ... don 't .
Mother ...
Please !
Noboru .
Chop my head off with this .
Do it now .
Because the next time I go crazy ...
I 'm sure I 'll kill you .
Chop my head off , Noboru !
Hurry up !
Aim at my neck !
If you don 't ... hurry up ...
Your brother .
Your sister .
You 'll end up like them !
Noboru .
What are you waiting for ?
Chop my head off .
If you don 't , it 'll come back to life and kill you !
Aim ...
Aim at my neck .
Aim at my ...
neck ...
" Aim at my neck . "
That 's what the voice in my mind kept saying .
If her head is chopped off ...
my mother may stop haunting people for good .
The sight of her was horrifying .
So I covered her with a coat and a mask ...
and hid her body inside .
What 's that ?
You mean the hole ?
Don 't you recognize it ?
Mika , are you in there ?
If you are , answer me .
Mika !
Mika ?
Mika .
Are you alright ?
How are you feeling ?
It must have hurt .
Ms. Yamashita .
I 'm so glad you 're alright .
I didn 't know about this cellar .
Could they be ... ?
Probably .
My brother and sister .
Are you okay ?
Mr. Matsuzaki .
Let 's take her to a hospital .
Careful , Mika .
Aim ...
at my ...
What is it ?
I can hear the voice .
It 's near .
Aim ...
at my ...
CHILD BECK HILL
Mika !
Are you in there ?
Mika ?
Answer me .
Ms. Yamashita !
Are you alright ?
Mika 's mother !
Where 's my Mika ? Is she alright ?
Mika !
Don 't go in there !
Taeko !
Don 't ...
Please stop .
I beg you .
Stop it !
Mother .
Forgive me .
Please .
Mother .
The knife .
To the hospital !
- Don 't worry about me . - But ...
Please ... get Mika out of here .
Go !
Run for your lives !
Mr. Matsuzaki !
Aim ...
at my neck ...
Mother ...
Come here .
Sorry to call you up like this .
What 's it about ?
I have to talk to Ai alone .
I 'll never ask you another favor .
Please .
Alright . But make it short .
Yes .
Ai , I 'm so sorry .
Forgive me .
Mommy ...
Ai !
Aim at my neck !